Guide to the United States Catholic China Bureau Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
United States Catholic China Bureau Records
1976-2011
RG 194
Yale University Divinity School Library
39
(94 boxes)
This record group consists of periodicals on China collected by the United States Catholic China Bureau as subject resources for its work, as well as material documenting the program activities of the Bureau. These periodicals document the Christian church in contemporary China.
United States Catholic China Bureau
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the USCCB, 2003, 2007, 2009, 2011
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Biographical / Historical
The United States Catholic China Bureau exists to foster communication and friendship with the people of China through sharing the values of the Gospel of Jesus Christ. It promotes understanding among American Catholics about the Catholic Church and the situation of Catholic communities in China. It seeks to engage the American Catholics in a new missionary partnership with Chinese Catholics.
Founded in 1989, with the encouragement of the National Conference of Catholic Bishops, the Bureau is sponsored by a cross-section of Roman Catholic organizations and individuals in the United States who share its purposes and goals. The USCCB offices is at Seton Hall University in South Orange, New Jersey.
Scope and Contents
The periodicals in Series I have been transferred to the Yale Divinity Library because of space restrictions at the USCCB office, and because it was thought that the materials would be more accessible to researchers if housed at an academic library.
Series II has been established to house a growing collection of material documenting the work of the Bureau.
Arrangement
Series I. Periodicals
Series II. Program Activities
China -- Church history -- 20th Century -- Periodicals; Catholic Church -- Missions -- Periodicals -- China; United States Catholic China Bureau
- Periodicals, 1976-2011; Series I
  - Actes Du Colloque
    - 1974 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - 1977 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - 1980 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - 1983 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - 1986 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - 1989 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - 1992 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - ACUCA News
    Scope and Contents
    Published in Hong Kong by Hong Kong Baptist University
    - Vol. 2 no. 4 (Winter 2002), vol. 3 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter 2003) (Box 31, Folder 178)
  - Amity Foundation
    Published in Nanjing China, by The Amity Foundation
    - 2000-2003 (Box 45, Folder 391)
    - Project Proposals, 2002-2003, 2005-2006 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 2004-2006 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Background Field Trip, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Amity Newsletter
    Published in Nanjing, China by The Amity Foundation
    - No. 2 (Spring 1986), no. 9 (Summer 1989)-no. 51 (Oct-Dec 1999), no. 53 (Apr-June 2000)-no. 63 (Oct-Dec 2002) (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - no. 72/1 (Jan-Mar 2005), no. 73/2 (Apr-Jun 2005), no. 74/3 (Jul-Sep 2005), no 75-76 (Oct 2005-Mar 2006), no. 77/2 (Apr-Jun 2006), no. 78/3 (Jul-Sep 2006) (Box 45, Folder 392)
    - no. 80/1 (Jan-Mar 2007), no. 81/2 (Apr-Jun 2007), no.82/3 (Jul-Sep 2007), no. 83/4 (Oct-Dec 2007) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - 2008-2010 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Amity News Service
    Published: Hong Kong: Amity Foundation Overseas Office
    - Vol. 1.1 (Jan. 1992)-10.5/6 (2001), vol. 10.9/10 (2001)-vol. 11.10/11 (2002); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 1, Folder 3-6)
    - vol. 11.5/6 (2001)-vol. 14.11/12 (2005) (Box 31, Folder 179)
    - vol. 15.1/2- vol. 16 (2006) (Box 45, Folder 393)
    - vol. 16.4-12 (2007) (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - 2008-2011 Jun (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Amity Re-Echo
    - Fall 1993, Spring 1994, Fall 1996, Winter 1996 (Box 31, Folder 180)
  - Amor Newsletter
    Published in Taiwan by Asia-Pacific Meeting for Religious Women, Asian Service Center
    - Vol. 7. no 2 (Oct-Dec 1997)- vol. 1 no. 1 (Dec 2003) (Box 31, Folder 181)
  - Asia Center
    Published in South Orange, New Jersey by Seton Hall University
    - Vol. 3 no. 1 (Nov 1995) (Box 31, Folder 182)
  - Asia Focus
    Published in Hong Kong by Union of Catholic Asian News
    - Vol 5 no. 27 (July 22, 1989), vol. 5 no. 32 (Sept. 2, 1989), vol 5 no. 35 (Sept. 23, 1989), vol. 5 no. 37 (Oct. 7, 1989), vol. 5 no. 41 (Nov. 4, 1989)-vol. 6 no. 24 (June 30, 1990), vol. 6 no. 26 (July 14, 1990)-vol. 7 no. 36 (Sept. 20, 1991), ["note: Asia Focus will not appear next week (9/27/1991); our next issue, #37, will be dated Oct. 4, 1991], vol. 7 no. 38 (Oct. 11, 1991), vol. 7, no. 39 (Oct. 18, 1991), vol. 7 no. 42 (Nov. 8, 1991), vol. 7 no. 44 (Nov. 22, 1991)-vol. 10 no. 17 (May 13, 1994), vol. 10 no. 19 (May 27, 1994)-vol. 11 no. 37 (Sept. 29, 1995), vol. 11 no. 39 (Oct. 20, 1995)-vol. 15 no. 43 (Nov. 19, 1999), vol. 15 no. 45 (Dec. 3, 1999)-vol. 16 no. 21 (June 2, 2000), vol. 16 no. 23 (Jun. 16, 2000)-vol. 16 no. 40 (Oct. 20, 2000), vol. 16 no.42 (Nov. 3, 2000)-vol. 17 no. 45 (Nov. 30, 2001), vol. 17 no. 47 (Dec. 17, 2001)- vol. 18 no. 40 (Oct. 18, 2002), vol. 18 no. 42 (Nov. 8, 2002)- vol. 18 no. 48 (Dec. 20, 2002); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 2–4)
    - Vol. 19 nos. 1-48 (Jan-Dec 2003); Vol. 20 nos. 1-48 (Jan-Dec 2004); Vol. 21 nos. 1-48 (Jan-Dec 2005) (Box 31, Folder 183-185)
    - Vol. 22 (2006); Vol. 23 (2007) (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - 2008 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - AsiaNetwork Exchange
    Published in Rock Island, Illinois by Augustana College
    - Vol. 7 no. 2 (Winter 1999) (Box 31, Folder 186)
  - Asia Pacific Advocate
    Published in New Jersey by the Asia Center of Seton Hall University
    - Winter (1999-2000) (Box 31, Folder 187)
  - APC Focus
    Published in Washington, DC by Asia Pacific Center for Justice and Peace
    - Nos. 1-13 and 15-16 (May/Jun 1996- May/Jun 1999) and (Sep- Oct 1998- Nov/ Dec 1999) (Box 32, Folder 188)
  - Asia View
    - Winter (1999-2000) (Box 32, Folder 189)
  - Beijing Review
    Published in Beijing, China by Beijing Review
    - Subject Index (Nos. 27-52, 1991), vol. 34 no. 27 (July 8-14, 1991), vol 34 no. 28 (July 15-21, 1991), vol. 34 no. 30 (July 29-Aug 4, 1991)-vol. 35 no. 24 (June 15-21, 1992), vol. 35 no. 26 (June 29-July 5, 1992)- vol. 36 no. 35 (Aug. 30- Sept. 5, 1993), vol. 37 no. 12 (Mar. 21-27, 1994)- vol. 37 no. 14 (Apr 4-10, 1994), vol. 37 no. 35 (Aug. 29-Sept. 4, 1994) [2 copies], vol. 40 no. 20 (May 19-25, 1997)-vol. 40 no. 39 (Sept. 29-Oct. 5, 1997); Also available at SML, LC Classification, non-circ, DS 777.55 P43 (Box 4–6)
    - Vol. 40 nos. 40-50 (Oct 1997-Nov 1998), vol. 41 nos. 1-7 (Jan 1998- Feb 1998) (Box 32, Folder 190-192)
  - Bridge
    Published in Shatin, N.T., Hong Kong by Tao Fong Shan Ecumenical Centre
    - No. 21 (Jan-Feb 1987) [photocopy], no. 34 (Mar-Apr 1989) [photocopy], no. 39 (Jan-Feb 1990), no. 44 (Nov-Dec 1990), no. 49 (Sept-Oct 1991)- no. 74 (Dec. 1995); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 6, Folder 33-34)
    - Nos. 75-86 (Feb 1996- Dec 1997) (Box 32, Folder 193)
    - No. 1 (Sep 1983) - no. 24 (Jul-Aug 1987), no. 28 (Apr- May1988)- no. 29 (Jun-Jul 1988), no. 31 (Oct-Nov 1988) - no. 37 (Sep-Oct 1989), no. 40 (Mar-Apr. 1990)- no. 43 (Sep-Oct 1990), no. 45 (Jan-Feb 1991)- no. 48 (Jul-Aug 1991) (Box 46, Folder 394-397)
  - Catholic Church in China
    in Chinese
    - Holdings: no. 1 (1990)-no. 4 (1990), no. 1 (1991)-no. 5 (1991), no. 1 (1992)-no. 5 (1992), no. 1 (1993)-no. 5 (1993), no. 1 (1994)-no. 6 (2000) (Box 7–8)
    - no. 1-6 (2004) (Box 43, Folder 375)
    - no.1 (2001)- no. 6 (2001), no. 1 (2002)- no. 6 (2002), no. 1 (2003)- no. 6(2003), no. 1 (2005)- no. 6 (2005) (1 of 2 boxes) (Box 32–33)
    - 1981-1986 (Box 47, Folder 398-399)
    - 1987-1988, no. 1-6 (2006) (Box 48, Folder 400-401)
    - 1980, no. 3 (Box 62, Folder 472)
    - 2007, no. 1-6 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - 2008 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 2009 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 2010 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - 2011 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Catholic Social Service Center, Xian Diocese, Newsletter
    - 2004-2006 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Catholic Social Service Office
    Published in China by the Catholic Social Service Office, Xi'an Diocese
    - Issue 2 (Jun-Aug 2003)- issue 4 (Jan-Mar 2004), issue 6 (Jul-Sep 2004), issue 3 (Jul-Sep 2005), issue 11 (2005) (Box 49, Folder 402)
  - China and Ourselves
    Published in Toronto by Canada China Program
    - Nos. 25/26 (May and July 1981), nos. 46/47 (summer/fall 1986), vol. 14 no. 4 (winter 1989)-vol. 18 no. 4 (winter 1993/94); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - China Bulletin
    - 1986 Mar, 1986 Dec (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - China Catholic Communication
    - Holdings: no. 6 (Jan. 1984), no. 8 (Jan. 1985)-issue 11 (July 1986), issue 18 (Jan. 1990)-issue 25 (June 1993), May/Jun. #51 (1990), July/Aug. #52 (1990), Jan./Feb. #55 (1991)-Aug.-Sept. #70 (1993), Nov./Dec. #72 (1993)-#80 (Box 9, Folder 47-50)
    - #81- #89, #91- #97, #99- #102, #104- #108, #112 (Box 44, Folder 389-390)
    - #114- #117 (Box 49, Folder 403)
    - 2007, #118 - 2011, #132 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - China Catholic News
    Published in Beijing by The Overseas Friendship Association of Catholic Bishops' Conference of China
    - No. 1 (Dec. 1995)-vol. 9 no. 4 (Dec. 1997) (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - vol. 10 no. 1 (Apr 1999), vol 12. no. 3 (Sep 1998), vol 13 no. 4 (Dec 1998), sum. 14 no. 1 (Mar 1999)- no. 4 (Dec 1999), (2000), (Apr 2001) (Box 33, Folder 198)
    - 2007 (nos. 1-2) (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - China Chronicles
    Published in Pasadena, CA by China Connection
    - 2006 (nos. 1-4); 2007 (nos. 1-4) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - 2008-2011 Fall (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - China Church News
    Published in Taiwan by the Jesuit China Service
    - Nos. 69- 74 (Mar 96- Dec 97) (Box 33, Folder 204)
  - China Council Quarterly (formerly China Information Bulletin )
    Published in Portland, Oregon by the Northwest Regional China Council
    - No. 63 (July-Sept. 1996)-no. 74 (Apr.-June 1999), no. 76 (Oct.-Dec. 1999), no. 78 (Apr.-June 2000) [photocopy]-no. 88 (Oct.-Dec. 2002) (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
    - nos. 89-92 (Jan- Mar 2003)- (Oct- Dec 2003) (Box 33, Folder 199)
    - 2006 (nos. 101-104) (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - China Cross Currents
    Published by Macau Ricci Institute
    - Nos. 3.3, 3.4 (2006), Nos. 4.1, 4.2 (2007) (Box 64, Folder 1-2)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - China Currents
    Published in Quezon City, Philippines by the Philippine-China Development Resource Center
    - Vol. 1 no. 1 (Jan-Mar 1996), vol. 7 no. 4 (Oct-Dec 1996), vol. 8 nos. 1-2 (Jan-Jun 1997) (Box 37, Folder 227)
  - China Exchange
    Published in North Turranmurra, NSW by Columban Mission Institute Sydney Centre for Churches and China
    - No. 6 (Aug 2001), no. 7 (Dec 2001), no. 9 (Jul 2002)- no. 13 (Dec 2003), no. 14 (Mar 2004), no. 16 (Dec 2004), no. 20 (Aug 2005), no. 21 (Nov 2005) (Box 33, Folder 200)
    - no. 15 (Sep 2004), no. 19 (Jun 2005), nos. 22-29 (2006-2007) (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - 2008 Mar - 2011 Aug (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - China Exchange News
    Published in Washington, DC by Committee on Scholarly Communication with China
    - Index vol. 1-10 (1973-1992), vol. 22 no. 3 (Fall 1994)-vol. 23 no. 3 (Fall 1995); Also at SML: E183.8 C5 C455 (LC)+ (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Spring 1986 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - China Heute: Informationen uber Religion und Christentum im chineisischen Raum
    Published in Sankt Augustin, Germany by China-Zentrum
    - Vol. 8 no. 1 (1989)-vol. 8 no. 4 (1989), vol. 9 no. 1 (1990) [2 copies]-vol. 21 no. 4-5 (2002); Also at Divinity Library: ZP C43897 (Box 10–12)
    - vol. 21 no.6 (2002), vol. 22 no.1-6 (2003), vol. 23 nos. 1-6 (2004), vol. 24 no. 1-6 (2005) (Box 33, Folder 201-203)
    - vol. 25 no. 1-6 (2006) (Box 49, Folder 404-405)
    - 2007 #1-6 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - 2009-2010 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - 2010-2011 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - China Information Bulletin (later China Council Quarterly )
    Published in Portland, Oregon: Northwest Regional China Council
    - Vol. 4 no. 4 (May 1994)- vol. 4 no. 6 (Sept. 1994), vol. 5 no. 1 (Dec. 1994)-vol. 5 no. 4 (June 1995) (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - China News Analysis
    Published in Hong Kong
    - No. 1392 (Sept. 1, 1989) [front page missing] no. 1429 (Feb. 15, 1991), no. 1431 (Mar. 15, 1991)-no. 1467 (Sept. 1, 1992), no. 1469 (Oct. 1, 1992)-no. 1533 (Apr. 15, 1995), no. 1535 (May 15, 1995)-no. 1544 Oct. 1, 1995), no. 1546 (Nov. 1, 1995)-no. 1550 (Index 1995); Also available at SML: DS 701 C344A (Box 12–13)
    - no. 1551 (Jan. 1, 1996)-no. 1552 (Jan. 15, 1996), no. 1554 (Feb. 15, 1996)- no. 1555 (Mar. 1, 1996), no. 1557 (Apr. 1, 1996)- no. 1558 (Apr. 15, 1996), no. 1559 (May 1, 1996)- no.1560 (May 15, 1996), no. 1562 (Jun. 15, 1996)- no. 1619 (Oct. 1, 1998), no. 1621 (Nov. 1, 1998)- no.1622 (Nov. 15, 1998), no. 1625 (Index 1998) (Box 50, Folder 406-407)
    - 1998 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - China News Update
    Published in New York by Presbyterian Church (U.S.A.), Program Agency
    - July 1986, Nov. 1988, Aug. 1989, Dec. 1989, Aug. 1990, Dec. 1990, March 1991, July 1991, Oct. 1991, Jan. 1992, May 1992, Sept. 1992, Jan. 1993, May 1993, Sept. 1993, Jan. 1994, Sept. 1994, Jan. 1995, May 1995, Sept. 1995, Jan. 1996, May 1996, May 1997, Sept. 1997, Jan. 1998, May 1998, Sept. 1998, Jan. 1999, Sept. 1999, Jan. 2000 [2 copies], May 2000, Sept. 2000; Also available at Divinity Library- Restricted Circulation Serial (Box 13, Folder 72)
    - Jan. 2001, May 2001, Sep. 2001, Jan. 2002, May 2002, Sep. 2002, Jan. 2003, May 2003, Sep. 2003, Jan. 2004, May 2004, Sep. 2004 (Box 34, Folder 204)
    - Sep. 2005, Jan. 2006, Sep. 2006 (Box 50, Folder 408)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - China Notes
    Published in New York by China Committee of the NCCC's Div. of Foreign Missions
    - Vol. 15 no. 1 (Winter 1976-77), vol. 19 no. 4 (Fall 1981), vol. 23 no. 4 (Autumn 1985), vol. 24 no. 1 (Winter 1985-1986), vol. 26 no. 3 (Summer 1988), vol. 27 no. 2 (Spring 1989)-vol. 30 no. 3 and 4 (Summer and Autumn 1992); Also available at Divinity Library: ZP C43905 (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - China Pictorial
    Published in Beijing, China by China Pictorial Publications
    - Vol. 579 no. 9 (1996) (Box 34, Folder 205)
  - China Reconstructs (later China Today )
    Published in Beijing by China Welfare Institute
    - Vol. 35 no. 1 (Jan. 1986), vol. 35 no. 2 (Feb. 1986), vol. 35 no. 3 (Mar. 1986), vol. 37 no. 3 (Mar. 1988); Also at SML: DS 701 C347+ (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - China Reflections
    Published by Columban Fathers
    - Vol. 1 nos. 1-3 (May-Nov 1996), vol. 2 nos. 1-3 (Feb-Jul 1997), vol. 3 nos 1-4 (Jan-Oct 1998), vol. 4 nos. 2-3 (Apr. and Jul 1999), vol. 6 nos. 3-4 (Sep and Dec 2001), vol. 7 nos. 1-4 (Mar-Dec 2002), vol. 8 nos. 1-3 (Mar-Sep 2003) (Box 34, Folder 206)
  - China Service Ventures Newsletter
    Published in St. Paul, Minnesota by China Service Ventures
    - No. 9 (Mar. 1, 2006)- no. 10 (Sep. 1, 2006) (Box 59, Folder 460)
    - 2007-2010 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - China Source
    Published in Wheaton, IL by China Source Partnering Resources with Vision
    - Summer 1996, Fall/Winter 1997, Spring 1998, Summer 1998, vol. 1 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter 1999), vol. 2 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter 2000), vol. 3 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter 2001), vol. 4 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter 2002), vol. 5 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter 2003), vol. 6 nos. 1-4 (Spring-Winter) (Box 34, Folder 207-209)
    - Fall 2002, vol. 5, no. 3 (Fall 2003)- no. 4 (Winter 2003), vol. 6, no. 3 (Fall 2004)- no. 4 (Winter 2004), vol. 7, no. 1 (Spring 2005)- no. 4 (Winter 2005) (Box 50, Folder 409)
    - 2006 (Vol. 8, nos. 1-4) (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - 2007-2008 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - China Sparks
    Published by China Sparks Vincentian Reflections on the Church in China
    - Vol. 4 nos. 2-3 (Sep-Dec 1999), vol. 5 nos. 1-3 (May-Dec 2000), vol. 6 no. 1 (Mar 2001), vol. 7 no. 2 (Nov 2001), vol. 8 no. 1 (Apr 2002), vol. 9 no. 2 (Sep 2002), vol. 9 no. 1-2 (Jan- Jun 2003), vol. 10 no. 3 (Dec. 2003), vol. 11 no. 1-2 (Jun-Dec 2004) (Box 34, Folder 210)
    - 2003-2005 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - China Study Journal
    Published in London by the Department for China Relations and Study
    - Vol. 5, no. 3 (Dec 1990)- vol. 6, no. 3 (Dec. 1991), vol. 7, no. 1 (Apr. 1992)- no. 3 (Dec. 1992), vol. 8, no. 1 (Apr 1993)- vol. 9, no. 1 (Aug. 1994), vol. 10, no. 3 (Dec. 1995) (Box 50–51)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - 1997 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - 1998 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - 1999 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - 2000 - 2001 Apr (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - 2001 Aug - 2002 Apr (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - 2002 Aug - 2003 Aug (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - 2003 Dec - 2004 Dec (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - China Study Project
    - Bulletins no. 6-11 (1978-1979) (Box 61, Folder 470)
    - Report and documentation; 1977 Jun, 1979 Nov (Box 62, Folder 471)
    - 1980 Jul - 1985 Nov (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - China Study Project Journal
    - 1986 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - 1987 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - 1988 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - China Talk
    Published in Hong Kong by China Liaison Office, World Division, Board of Global Ministries, United Methodist Church
    - Vol. 3 no. 4 (Oct. 1978), vol. 4 no. 2 (Mar./Apr. 1979), vol. 4 nos. 5 and 6 (Dec. 1979), vol. 9 no. 1 (Feb. 1984), vol. 10 nos. 2 and 3 (Apr./May 1985), vol 11 nos. 1 and 2 (Mar. 1986)-Special Issue (May 3, 1987), vol. 12 nos. 4 and 5 (Sept. 1987)-vol. 13 no. 4 (Oct. 1988), vol. 14 no. 2 (Apr. 1989)-vol 22 1st and 2nd quarters (Mar. 1997) [ 2 copies], vol. 23 1st quarter (May 1998)-vol. 24 1st and 2nd quarters (Apr. 1999); Also available at Divinity Library - Restricted Circulation Serial (1 of 2 boxes) (Box 13–14)
  - China: The Continuing Challenge
    - 2001, Nov 27-29 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - China Today (formerly China Reconstructs )
    - Vol. 39 no. 4 (Apr. 1990), Index (1991), vol. 40 no. 3 (March 1991-vol. 50 no. 12 (Dec. 2001); Also available at SML: DS701 C347 (1 of 5 boxes) (Box 14–18)
    - Vol. 51 nos. 1-4 (Jan-Apr 2002) and 7-12 (Jul-Dec 2002), vol.52 nos. 1-12 (Jan- Dec 2003), vol. 53 nos. 1-12 (Jan-Dec 2004), vol. 54 nos. 1-12 (Jan- Dec 2005), vol. 55 nos. 1-12 (Jan-Dec 2006) (1 of 3 boxes) (Box 34–36)
    - Vol. 56 nos. 1-5 (Jan-May 2007) (Box 51, Folder 415-416)
    - Vol. 46 nos. 6-12 (Jun-Dec 2007) (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
    - 2008 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - China Update
    Published in New Haven, CT by the Yale-China Association
    - Vol. 5 no. 2 (spring 1985), vol. 10 nos. 3 and 4 (fall/winter 1990)-vol. 11 no. 4 (winter 1991); Also available at SML, Manuscripts and Archives (Non-Circulating), Yp37 +C45 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - China Update (Belgium)
    Published in Oud-Heverlee, Belgium by J. Spae
    - Spring 1983-summer 1986, spring 1987-Sept-Dec 1989, Church in China: a 1989 Digest; also available at Mudd Library, Divinity: ZP C4393 (Box 18–19)
  - Chinese American Forum
    Published in St. Louis County, Missouri by The Chinese American Forum
    - Vol. 12 (Winter 1997), vol. 13 no. 1 (July 1998) [typo reads "vol. 14"], vol. 13 no. 4 (Apr. 1998), vol. 15 no. 3 (Jan. 2000) [2 copies], vol. 16 no. 1 (July 2000)-vol. 18 no. 2 (Oct. 2002) (Box 20, Folder 110-113)
    - Jun 1999, vol. 18 no. 3 (Jan 2003), vol. 18 no. 4 (Apr 2003) (Box 37, Folder 225)
  - Chinese Catholic Digest: "Faith and Outreach"
    Published in Monterey Park, CA by United Chinese Apostolate
    - Vol. 1 no. 1 (Oct 1998), vol. 2 no. 1 (Feb 1999), vol. 3 no. 3 (Jun 1999) (Box 37, Folder 226)
  - Chinese Cross Currents
    - 2004, #1-2 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - 2004, #3-4 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - 2005, #1-2 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - 2006-2007 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Chinese Information and Culture Center (CICC) Currents
    Published in New York by Chinese Information and Culture Center
    - No. 15 (Nov/Dec 1994)-no. 26 (Sept/Oct 1996) (Box 20, Folder 114)
  - Chinese Language newsletters
    - Materials in Chinese (Box 60, Folder 468)
  - Chinese Theological Review
    - 1985-1988 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - 1993-1996 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - 1997-2000 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - 2001-2011 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Columban China Exhange
    Published in North Turramurra NSW by Columban Centre for Churches and China
    - No. 1 (Apr. 1998), no. 2 (Jul. 1998), Oct. 1998, no. 3 (Nov. 1998), no. 4 (May 1999), no. 5 (Dec. 1999), no. 6 (May 2001) (Box 37, Folder 228)
  - Columban Mission
    Published in St. Columbans, NE
    - (Sep./Oct. 1998), (Oct. 2001) (Box 37, Folder 229)
    - (May 2006), (Jun/Jul 2006), (Dec 2007) (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - 2006 Oct - 2009 Dec (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - 2010 Jan - 2011 Sep (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Comboni Press Network
    Published in Cincinnati, OH by the News Service of the Comboni Missionaries
    - Vol. 3 no. 1 (Mar 1996), vol. 5 no. 3 (May 1998), vol. 5 no. 4 (Jul 1998), vol. 5 no. 6 (Nov 1998) vol. 6 no. 3 (May 1999) (Box 37, Folder 230)
  - Consultazione sulla Chiesa in Cina
    - 2002 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence
    Published in Manila, [Philippines] and Hong Kong by Jesuit China Service
    - No. 4 (Aug. 1982) [photocopy], no. 12 (May/June 1983) [photocopy], no. 33 (Jan. 1989)-no. 48 (Aug. 1991), supplement: Religion in China Today, no. 51 (Feb. 1992)-no. 53 (June 1992), no. 55 (Oct. 1992)-no. 68 (Dec. 1995) (Box 20, Folder 115-116)
  - Courrier Verbiest
    Published by the Fondation Verbiest
    - Vol. 5 (Dec. 1993), vol. 6 (Jun. 1994), vol. 7 (Jun. 1995), vol. 7 (Dec. 1995) vol. 8 (Dec 1996), vol. 9 (Dec 1997), vol. 10 (Jun 1998), vol. 10 (Dec 1998), vol. 11 (Jun 1999), vol. 11 (Dec 1999), vol. 12 (Jun 2000), vol. 12 (Dec 2000), vol. 13 (Jun 2001), vol. 13 (Dec 2001), vol. 14 (Jun 2002), vol. 14 (Dec 2002), vol. 15 (Jun 2003), vol. 15 (Dec. 2003), vol. 16 (Jan.-Dec. 2004) (Box 37, Folder 331-332)
    - Nr. 2 (Feb 2005) - nr. 3 (Jun. 2005), vol. 17 (Dec. 2005), vol. 18 (Jui 2006) (Box 52, Folder 417)
    - 2004, 2007-2010 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - The Cresset
    - 2006, 2008-2009 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Current
    Published in Berkeley, CA by the Educational Resources and Referrals-China (ERRC)
    - (Summer 1996)- (Winter1996), (Summer 1997)- (Winter 1997), (Winter 1999), (Spring 1999), (Fall-Winter 2000), vol. 1 (Feb. 2002)- vol. 3 (Dec. 2003) (Box 39, Folder 350)
    - 2004 Dec-2011 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Current History
    - 1990-2001 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 2003-2008 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Dialogue
    Published in San Francisco, CA by The Dui Hua Foundation
    - Issues 22-23 (Winter- Spring 2006), issue 25 (Fall 2006) (Box 52, Folder 418)
    - 2007, 2010 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Eglises D'Asie
    - 2008 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - 2008-2009 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - European Ecumenical China Communication
    Published in China by The European Ecumenical China Meeting
    - No. 1 (1992)- no. 5 (2003) (Box 52, Folder 419-422)
  - FABC Papers
    - 92e - 115 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Faith
    Published in Shijiazhuang,Hebei [China]: Faith Press; (see also http://www.chinacatholic.org/english/)
    - No. 67 (Nov. 1, 1997), no. 81 (Oct. 15, 1998), no. 85 (Jan. 1, 1999)-no. 87 (Feb. 1, 1999), no. 89 (Apr. 1, 1999), no. 91 (May 1, 1999)- no. 94 (July 15, 1999), no. 96 (Sept. 1, 1999)-no. 105 (Mar. 1, 2000), no. 107 (Mar. 1, 2000)-no. 119 (Oct. 1, 2000), no. 121 (Nov. 1, 2000)-no. 156 (Apr. 15, 2002), no. 158 (May 15, 2002)-no. 172 (Dec. 15, 2002) (Box 21, Folder 117-121)
    - no. 173 (Jan. 1, 2003)- no. 203 (Dec. 23, 2003), no. 2006 (Feb. 1, 2004)- no. 209 (Mar. 15, 2004), no. 213 (May 15, 2004)- no. 220 (Sep. 1, 2004), no. 222 (Oct. 1, 2004)- no. 227 (Dec. 15, 2004), no. 233 (Mar. 15, 2005)- no. 245 (Sep. 15, 2005), no. 247 (Oct. 15, 2005)- no. 248 (Nov. 1, 2005), no. 250 (Dec. 1, 2005)- no. 251 (Dec. 15, 2005) (Box 37–38)
    - No. 252 (Jan. 1, 2006)- no. 255 (Feb. 1, 2006), no. 259 (Mar. 10, 2006)- no. 303 (Jun. 1, 2007) (Box 52, Folder 423-425)